Guide to the Judith P. Vladeck Papers WAG.177
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Judith P. Vladeck Papers
undated
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Vladeck, Judith P.
WAG.177
188 Linear Feet in 188 boxes record cartons.
Judith Pomarlen Vladeck (1923-2007) was a prominent labor and civil rights lawyer, and specialist in cases involving allegations of workplace discrimination against women, winning major cases against Wall Street investment firms, Chase Manhattan Bank, Western Electric and the City University of New York, among other powerful opponents. This collection contains case files for Kyriazi v. Western Electric as well as case files documenting the landmark sex discrimination case of Professor Lilia Melani against the City University of New York.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Historical/Biographical Note
Judith Pomarlen Vladeck (1923-2007) was a prominent labor and civil rights lawyer, and a senior partner in the Manhattan law firm of Vladeck, Waldman, Elias and Engelhard at the time of her death. She was a graduate of Hunter College and Columbia University Law School. In 1957 she joined the law firm of her husband, Stephen Vladeck, a labor lawyer. Over the years the firm represented many New York area unions. Judith Vladeck became a specialist in cases involving allegations of workplace discrimination against women, winning major cases against Wall Street investment firms, Chase Manhattan Bank, Western Electric and the City University of New York, among other powerful opponents.
Arrangement
This collection has not been arranged by an archivist; materials are in the order in which they were received from the donor.
Scope and Contents
The first series of boxes are case files for Kyriazi v. Western Electric. Most of the rest of the collection consists of case files documenting the landmark sex discrimination case of Professor Lilia Melani against the City University of New York, but include some additional correspondence, reference material and case files.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by Judith P. Vladeck in 2004. The accession number 2004.029 is associated with this gift.
Reports.; Correspondence.; Sex discrimination in employment.; Universities and Colleges -- Employees; Sex discrimination against women.; Lawyers.; Legal files.; Women lawyers.; Clippings (information artifacts); New York (State); New York (N.Y.); Melani, Lilia; City University of New York; City University of New York--Employees; Vladeck, Waldman, Elias and Engelhard; Vladeck, Judith P.; Vladeck, Judith P.
- Inventory, 1
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Legal Correspondence, Jul 1980 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Legal Correspondence, Aug 1980 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Legal Correspondence, Sep 1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Legal Correspondence, Oct 1980 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Legal Correspondence, Nov 1980 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Legal Correspondence, Dec 1980 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Legal Correspondence, Jan 1981 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Legal Correspondence, Feb 1981 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Legal Correspondence, Mar 1981 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Legal Correspondence, Apr 1981 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Kyriazi- Plaintiffs Amended Pre-Trial Memorandum (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Appendix to Plaintiffs Amended Pre-Trial Memorandum (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Extra Papers, Jun 1977-Oct 1978 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Extra Legal, Post-Oct 30, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Extra Papers: Defendants Proposed Findings of Fact and Conclusions of Law (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Extra Papers: Defendants Proposed Findings of Fact and Conclusions of Law (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Extra Papers: Plaintiffs Memorandum in Reply to Defendants Proposed Findings of Fact and Conclusions of Law (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Letters Received Regarding Settlement (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Extra: Legal (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Extra Papers: Certified Petition (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Legal Correspondence: Form Letters to Late Filers and Applicants/ RE: Masters Reports (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Bali Valiante/Objector Before LSH (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 67. Patricia (Jankowski) Vasconi Objector Schedule I #342 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 11. Jessie Wade/Objector Schedule III #240A (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 68. Yvonne Walls/ Objector Schedule I #346 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 17. Carol Wells/ Objector Schedule IV #351 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Sherron White/ Objector (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 69. Helen Williams/Objector Schedule I #354A (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 70. Patricia Williams/Objector Schedule I #358 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 71. Lillian Melvin Wilson/Objector Schedule I #360 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Anna Maria Wimmer/ Objector (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 12. Pamela Witkowski/ Objector Schedule III #361 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 72. Anna Zabnicki/Objector Schedule I #366A (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric:9. Betty Simmons/Objector Schedule II #309 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 60. Myrtle Simmons/Objector Schedule I #312 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric:10. Jeanne A. Simonson/Objector/Late Filer #311 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Rachel Singleton/Objector Before LSH (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Marion Sita/Objector/Late Filer (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Lillian Solomon/ Objector/Late Filer (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 61. Sandra Spears/ Objectors Schedule I #322 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Gail Stanizewski/ Objector Schedule I #324 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 7. Helen A. Prussek/ Objector/ Late Filer #270 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 1. Audrey Adams/Objector Schedule I #1 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 2. Perlie Alston/ Objector Schedule I #3 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 3. Susie Amato/Objector Schedule I #5 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Angelina A. Annolina/Objector/ Late Filer (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 4. Linda Ascolsese/ Objector Schedule I #9 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 5. Maria Avila/ Objector Schedule I #12 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Mary Barnes/ Objector Before LSH #12A (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Lillie Belk/ Objector/ Late Filer (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 6. Alsacia Berrios/ Objector Schedule I #20 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 7. Valerie Bomba/ Objector Schedule I #25 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 8. Blanca Bonilla/ Objector Schedule I #28 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 9. Graciette Borges/ Objector Schedule I #29 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 1. Beatrice Branch/ Objector Schedule III #32 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 10. Persis Brandon/ Objector Schedule I #33 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 11. Delores Brown/ Objector Schedule I #33A (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 12. Sharon Caines/ Objector Schedule I #42 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 13. Carol Ann Calamito/Objector Schedule I #45 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Agnes Cambell/Objector (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 2. Agnes Camphice/Objector Schedule III #47 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 1. Rose M. Carlo/Objector/Late Filer #52 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 15. Lessie Carr/Objector Schedule I #53 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 3. Sarah Carson/Objector Schedule III #55 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 4. Joan Chambers/Objector Schedule III #283A (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 63. Lola Tatum/Objector Schedule I #328 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 64. Mary Taylor/Objector Schedule I (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 65. Mildred Taylor/Objector Schedule I #330 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 66. Patricia Tchorzewski/Objector Schedule I #331 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 3. Nancy Jesch/Objector Schedule II #163 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 33. Beatrice Johnson/Objector Schedule I #166 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Betty Jones/Objector (No objection) (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Hattie Joyner/Objector Cases before LSH (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 34. Hattie Koschal/Objector Schedule I #180 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 4. Evelyn E. Kost/Objector/Late Filer #181 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 5. Catherine T. Kucewicz/Objector/Late Filer/ #182 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Thelma Little/Objector (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Ms. DErrico/Objector/Late Filer (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Geraldine Duda/Objector (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Elizabeth Edwards/Objector Before TFC #100A (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 22. Stella Errigo/Objector Schedule I #103 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 23. Linda Flanigan/Objector Schedule I #108 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 24. Vitoria Flemming Schedule I #109 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 25. Fernell Monney Gatlin/Objector Schedule I #121 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 26. Lois Bouldin Gill/Objector Schedule I #122 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Ester Gonzalez/Objector (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 27. Peggy Graves/Objector Schedule I #136A (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Vivian Green/Objector (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 28. Helen Griffin/Objector Schedule I #141 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 29. Nora Guttierrez/ Objector Schedule I #146 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Christine Cheatum/Objector (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 16. Thelma Cherry/Objector Schedule I #62 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Carmela Cikanovich/Objector Before LSH #63B (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 14. Jonie Colbert/Objector Schedule I #46 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 17. Martha Coleman/Objector Schedule I #70 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 18. Ethel Cunningham/Objector Schedule I #79A (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 19. Emma Curry/Objector Schedule I #83 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Eileen Dacus (Farley Davis)/Objector/Late Filer (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 20. Mary Ann Dailey/Objector Schedule I (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Classification of Late Filers/Objectors (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 35. Josephine Lombardi/Objector Schedule I #191B (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Eileen Long/Objector/Late Filer (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Evie Long/Objector/Late Filer (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Essie Lee Lott/Objector (no objection) (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 38. Marie P. Lynch/Objector Schedule I #195 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 39. Clara Mack/Objector Schedule I #198 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 40. Lanche Macklin/Objector Schedule I #200 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Dorothea Magrine/Objector/Late Filer (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 6. Joyce Mangiapone/Objector Schedule III #207 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 7. Irene Masco/Objector Schedule III #212 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 41. Anna Maute/Objector Schedule I #212B (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 42. Henrietta McClelland/Objector Schedule I #215 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 43. Delores McQueen/Objector Schedule I #218 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Gladys McRae/Objector Schedule I #219A (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 45. Patricia Mellet/Objector Schedule I #220A (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 6. Bertha B. Miller/Objector/Late Filer #226 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Dolores Mitchell/Objector (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 8. Mary Mitchell/Objector Schedule III #229 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Valdette Mohammed/Objector/LF (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 47. Dorothy Molette/Objector Schedule I #233 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 46. Mary Moldin/Objector Schedule I #232 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Virginia Morton/Objector Before LSH (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 48. Selena Murray/Objector Schedule I #239A (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 18. Susie Najmowski/Objector Schedule IV #343B (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 49. Isabella Nazzaro (Adolese)/Objector Schedule I #241 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 5. Dorothy Hannah/Objector Schedule III #149 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 2. Virginia L. Harley/Objector/Late Filer #150 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 31. Bernice Hicks/Objector Schedule I #151B (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Myrtle Hicks/Objector (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Marie M. Hill/Objector Before TFC 0 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 30. Theresa K. Hudson/Objector Schedule I #159 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 32. Geraldine Jacocks/Objector Schedule I #162 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 54. Will Mae Resse (McKenzie)/Objector Schedule I #277 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 10. Cheryl Reeves/Objector Schedule III #278 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 15. C. W. Rivers/Objector Schedule IV #59A (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 55. Margaret Ruth/Objector Schedule I #290 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 56. Rose Ann Safonte/Objector Schedule I #291 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 57. Dorothy Sanders/Objector Schedule I #295 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 58. Elva Scruggs/Objector Schedule I #302 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 59. Mary Senesi/Objector Schedule I #303 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 10. Sylvia Pritchard/Objector Schedule IV #268 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Irene Radomski/Objector/Late Filer (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 9. Naomi Raiford/Objector Schedule III #272 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Edna Rasberry/Objector/Late Filer (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 50. Krystymna Okoszko/Objector Schedule I #246 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Madeline Pettrize/Objector/Late Filer (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 51. Antoinette Olsen/Objector Schedule I #246A (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Miriam Checorski Podesfinski/Objector/Late Filer (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Maria Poiteven/Objector/Late Filer (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 8. Mary Reed/Objector/Late Filer #276 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Appendix of Plaintiff-Appellee/Cross-Appellant Volume II (pp. A601-A1210) (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Appendix of Plaintiff-Appellee/Cross-Appellant Volume I (pp. A1-A600) (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Motion to Modify Consent Decree Structural Volume II- Subject to Protective Order (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Client No. 7-193 Class Member and Employee Inquiries KS (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Priority Hiring List A: (Former Employees Who Refused an Offer of Reemployment. Specific Reasons Noted.) (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - W.E. Calls- JPC: Class Member and Employee Inquiries (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Priority Hiring List A Complete 10-7-81 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Kathleen Barry 7-193 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - File Indexes and Document Location (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Affidavit- Judith Vladeck (Attorneys Fees) (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Western Electric Settlement Fund The Kyriazi Matter Check Register Report No. 1, Nov 19, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence of Class Members Given to Goldstein to use for his report of 9/8/84 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Transfile #3- 13- Request for Ruling on the Tax Status of Fund Monies. To: IRS/ From: Hellring and Campion, Sep 11, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Goldsteins Report to Stern on Expressed Opinions of Classmembers to Proposal Order 9/18/84. Also Enclosed: 8/12/84 Transcript., Aug 12, 1984 and Sep 18, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - 7-193 Scheduling Conference Transript (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - 7-193 Claim of Linda Siegel Genaro (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - 7-193 Claim of Levenia DeBerry (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - 7-193 Claim of Irene M. Campenelli (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - 7-193 Claim of Patricia J. Openshaw (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - 7-193 Claim of Lola A. Powell (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - 7-193 Claim of Christine Kelly (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - 7-193 Claim of Addie Sessons (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - 7-193 Claim of Michele Franzoni (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Kyriazi Legal Correspondence, Jan-Jun 1983 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Kyriazi Legal Correspondence, Jul-Dec 1983 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Kyriazi Classmember Correspondence, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 1-12 Structural Aii (3rd Mandamus), Mar-May 1979 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - File O-p-2 3rd Mandamus Kyriaza Aii Part 2 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - 1st Distribution Kyriazi As per JPV: Eunice Scott/Kyriazi Monitoring: Correspondence within Class/Kyriazi Distribution (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Kyriazi Structural Ai Second Mandamus O-P1 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 9/11/79 Affidavit of Lynch on VEV Billing for Dec. & July 1973- See B-2 Structural, Sep 11, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 9/11/79 Affidavit of Lynch on VEV Billing for Oct. & Jan. 1974- See B-2 Structural, Sep 11, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 9/11/79 Affidavit of Lynch on VEV Billing for Nov. & April 1975- See B-2 Structural, Sep 11, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 9/11/79 Affidavit of Lynch on VEV Billing for Dec. & July 1976- See B-2 Structural, Sep 11, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 9/11/79 Affidavit of Lynch on VEVE Billing for Oct. & April 1977- See B-2 Structural, Sep 11, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 9/11/79 Affidavit of Lynch on VEVE Billing for Feb. & Jan. 1978- See B-2 Structural, Sep 11, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Third Circuit Court of Appeals- Docket No. 79-2715/ 79-2716/ 79-1564Stage II: One of two Structurals October 9th. (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Third Circuit Court of Appeals- Docket No. 80-1830/80-1831-Stage II: Structural VI- Rejected Applicants Appeals (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Third Circuit Court of Appeals- Docket No. 79-2715/ 79-2716/ 79-1564Stage II: Structural I-A. Starting #23-# ? IV (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Millicent Wright- Briefs Submitted by Kyriazi. W.E. & Ms. Wright (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Maternity Leave (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: (Nos. 79-1564/ 79-2715/ 79-2716) Appeal-Appendix-Volumes I-III (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - D-16, D-17: Summary of References re: Wage Differentials between men and women in testimony of John E. Ullmann (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Summaries of Pertinent References RE: 1-Purported unwillingness of women to assume responsibility. 2- Women as second: wage-earners (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Ullmann Trial Testimony/ Legal Colloquies (Ullmann) (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Schedule A/ Joint Appendix (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Articles referred to in Ullmann Trial Testimony (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Vladeck, Elias, Vladeck & Engelhard, P.C.: Research Files From Appeal to Thrid Circuit- 1. Liability Findings. (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Kyriaki Cleo Kyriazi v. Western Electric Company, Et Al.: Plaintiffs Memorandum in Reply to Defendants Proposed Findings of Fact and Conclusions of Law. (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Kyriaki Cleo Kyriazi v. Western Electric Company, Et Al.: Plaintiffs Memorandum of Law on Classwide and Individual Remedies (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Post-Settlement Transcripts, Nov 7, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Post-Settlement Transcripts, Mar 29, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Post-Settlement Transcripts, Nov 11, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Post-Settlement Transcripts, Oct 12, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Post-Settlement Transcripts, Nov 17, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Post-Settlement Transcripts: Memorandum of Law in Support of Plaintiffs Motion to Modify Consent Decree (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Post-Settlement Transcripts: Transcript of Settlement Confirmation Hearing, Jul 24, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Post-Settlement Transcripts: Transcript of Status Conference, Jul 31, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Post-Settlement Transcripts: Transcript of Affirmative Action Plan Hearing, Dec 29, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Post-Settlement Transcripts: Transcript of Proceedings (?), Oct 19, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Post-Settlement Transcripts: Transcript of Proceedings (?), Nov 30, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Post-Settlement Transcripts: Transcript of Affirmative Action Plan Hearing, Dec 2, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Post-Settlement Transcripts: Transcript of Status Conference, May 5, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Post-Settlement Transcripts: Transcript of Proceedings (?), Jun 29, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Post-Settlement Transcripts: Transcript of Proceedings (?), Jun 2, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Post-Settlement Transcripts: Transcript of Status Conference, Sep 19, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Post-Settlement Transcripts: Transcript of Affirmative Action Plan Hearing, Dec 5, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Post-Settlement Transcripts: Status Conference, Dec 10, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Post-Settlement Transcripts: Transcript of Proceedings (?), Nov 30, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Post-Settlement Transcripts: Hearing for Coordinator on Inquiry From Howard Goldberger, Esq., Oct 28, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 22)